const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'ἀγαπάω',
    answers: ['ik heb lief', 'ik bemin'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'γεννάω',
    answers: ['ik verwek', 'ik baar', 'ik geef leven'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'γεννάομαι',
    answers: ['ik word geboren'],
    explanation: '(passief)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐρωτάω',
    answers: ['ik vraag', 'ik ondervraag'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐπερωτάω',
    answers: ['ik vraag', 'ik ondervraag'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πλανάω',
    answers: ['ik misleid', 'ik doe dwalen'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τιμάω',
    answers: ['ik eer'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐπιτιμάω',
    answers: ['ik wijs terecht', 'ik berisp'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'καυχάομαι',
    answers: ['ik roem op', 'ik roem in'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ζάω',
    answers: ['ik leef'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δικαιόω',
    answers: ['ik rechtvaardig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πληρόω',
    answers: ['ik vul aan'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'σταυρόω',
    answers: ['ik kruisig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'φανερόω',
    answers: ['ik maak duidelijk', 'ik maak bekend'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson40Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson40-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 40 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson40Vocabulary
